<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for the indicator 6-2-1, translated into en</message>
	<data>Objective 6. Guarantee access for all to sustainably managed water supply and sanitation services6.2 By 2030, ensure access for all, under equitable conditions, to adequate sanitation and hygiene services and end open defecation, paying special attention to the needs of women and girls and people in vulnerable situations6.2.1. % of the population with access to adequate sanitation5/1/2020 12:00:00 AMBurundi Institute of Statistics and Economic Studies (ISTEEBU) / REGIDESONDAYISENGA Modest / WAKANA FerdinandSocial Studies and Statistics and Poverty Monitoring Service &quot;SESSSP&quot; / MHEM statistics and planning serviceHead of “Social Studies and Statistics and Poverty Monitoring” service / SDG focal point at MHEM(+257) 79401937 / (+ 257) 799772981156 BUJUMBURAndayimode2010@gmail.com / wakanafer@yahoo.frThis is the percentage of the population with access to improved sanitation facilities. These improved facilities include flush toilets with septic tanks, traditional improved or ventilated latrines, and sewage-connected latrines. The excreta treatment system is considered adequate if it is private (not shared) and if it prevents human contact with human excrementPercentageHousehold surveysData are collected from household surveys using the “household” questionnaireThe probable date of the next collection will be 2020In 2021ISTEEBU / Ministry of Hydraulics, Energy and MinesISTEEBU is responsible for compiling this indicator at the national levelISTEEBU is the body recognized by the Burundian government for the collection, processing and dissemination of official statistics helping in planning and decision-making.The indicator is relevant because it reflects the level of coverage of the population in terms of sanitation, an essential element for social well-being, in this case good health.Updating the indicator most often requires a household survey which requires a lot of resources. The indicator cannot be calculated by gender.Ratio of ordinary households connected to a sump, ditch, main collector and soak-off well and all ordinary households, expressed as a percentageThe results of the survey are validated at two levels: technical validation and official validation before publication. Administrative data are validated by the technical committee for statistical information (CTIS)The indicator is available at national level, province, area of residence (Total; Urban area; Rural area)The indicator can be compared to other indicators of the same type at regional and international levelAnnual report of the Ministry of Water, Energy and Mines.</data>
</root>
