<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for indicator 6-2-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en">Objective 6. Guarantee access for all to sustainably managed water supply and sanitation services6.2 By 2030, ensure access for all, under equitable conditions, to adequate sanitation and hygiene services and end open defecation, paying special attention to the needs of women and girls and people in vulnerable situations6.2.1. % of the population with access to adequate sanitation5/1/2020 12:00:00 AMBurundi Institute of Statistics and Economic Studies (ISTEEBU) / REGIDESONDAYISENGA Modest / WAKANA FerdinandSocial Studies and Statistics and Poverty Monitoring Service &quot;SESSSP&quot; / MHEM statistics and planning serviceHead of “Social Studies and Statistics and Poverty Monitoring” service / SDG focal point at MHEM(+257) 79401937 / (+ 257) 799772981156 BUJUMBURAndayimode2010@gmail.com / wakanafer@yahoo.frThis is the percentage of the population with access to improved sanitation facilities. These improved facilities include flush toilets with septic tanks, traditional improved or ventilated latrines, and sewage-connected latrines. The excreta treatment system is considered adequate if it is private (not shared) and if it prevents human contact with human excrementPercentageHousehold surveysData are collected from household surveys using the “household” questionnaireThe probable date of the next collection will be 2020In 2021ISTEEBU / Ministry of Hydraulics, Energy and MinesISTEEBU is responsible for compiling this indicator at the national levelISTEEBU is the body recognized by the Burundian government for the collection, processing and dissemination of official statistics helping in planning and decision-making.The indicator is relevant because it reflects the level of coverage of the population in terms of sanitation, an essential element for social well-being, in this case good health.Updating the indicator most often requires a household survey which requires a lot of resources. The indicator cannot be calculated by gender.Ratio of ordinary households connected to a sump, ditch, main collector and soak-off well and all ordinary households, expressed as a percentageThe results of the survey are validated at two levels: technical validation and official validation before publication. Administrative data are validated by the technical committee for statistical information (CTIS)The indicator is available at national level, province, area of residence (Total; Urban area; Rural area)The indicator can be compared to other indicators of the same type at regional and international levelAnnual report of the Ministry of Water, Energy and Mines.
			</language>
			<language lang="fr">Objectif 6. Garantir l’accès de tous à des services d’alimentation en eau et d’assainissement gérés de façon durable6.2 D’ici à 2030, assurer l’accès de tous, dans des conditions équitables, à des services d’assainissement et d’hygiène adéquats et mettre fin à la défécation en plein air, en accordant une attention particulière aux besoins des femmes et des filles et des personnes en situation vulnérable6.2.1. % de la population ayant accès à un assainissement adéquat5/1/2020 12:00:00 AMInstitut de Statistiques et d’Etudes Economiques du Burundi (ISTEEBU) /REGIDESONDAYISENGA Modeste /WAKANA FerdinandService Etudes et Statistiques Sociales et Suivi de la Pauvreté &quot;SESSSP&quot;/ service statistique et planification du MHEMChef de service « Etudes et Statistiques Sociales et Suivi de la Pauvreté »/ Point focal ODD au MHEM(+257) 79401937 /(+257) 799772981156 BUJUMBURAndayimode2010@gmail.com / wakanafer@yahoo.frC’est le pourcentage de la population ayant accès à des installations hygiéniques améliorées. Ces installations améliorées incluent les toilettes à chasse d’eau avec fosse septique, des latrines traditionnelles améliorées ou ventilées, latrines raccordées aux égouts. Le système de traitement des excréments est considéré adéquat s’il est privé (non partagé) et s’il empêche tout contact humain avec l’excrément humainPourcentageEnquêtes auprès des ménagesLes données sont collectées à partir des enquêtes auprès des ménages en utilisant le questionnaire « ménage »La date probable de la prochaine collecte sera 2020En 2021ISTEEBU/Ministère de l’hydraulique, énergie et minesL’ISTEEBU est  responsable de la compilation de cet indicateur au niveau nationalL’ISTEEBU est l’organe reconnu par le gouvernement burundais pour la collecte, le traitement et la diffusion des statistiques officielles aidant dans la planification et la prise de décision.L’indicateur est pertinent car il rend compte du niveau de couverture de la population en matière d’assainissement, élément indispensable pour le bien-être social, à l’occurrence la bonne santé.La mise à jour de l’indicateur nécessite  le plus souvent une enquête auprès des ménages qui exige beaucoup de moyens. L’indicateur ne pas être calculé par sexe.Rapport entre les ménages ordinaires connectés à un puisard, rigole, collecteur principal et puits perdu et tous les ménages ordinaires, exprimé en pourcentageLes résultats de l’enquête sont validés à deux niveaux : validation technique et validation officielle avant la publication. Les données administratives sont validées par le comité technique de l’information statistique (CTIS)L&apos;indicateur est disponible au niveau national, province, Milieu de résidence  (Total; Milieu urbain; Milieu rural)L’indicateur peut être comparé aux autres indicateurs du même type au niveau régional et internationalRapport annuel du Ministère de l’hydraulique, énergie et des mines.
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
