<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for indicator 9-3-1, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en">Objective 9. Build a resilient infrastructure, promote sustainable industrialization that benefits everyone and encourage innovation9.3 Increase, especially in developing countries, the access of enterprises, especially small industrial enterprises, to financial services, including loans on affordable terms, and their integration into value chains and markets9.3.1 Proportion of small businesses in total industry value addedThe proportion of &quot;small firms&quot; in total industry value added represents the share of manufacturing value added of small manufacturing firms in total manufacturing value added. A company is the smallest legal unit that constitutes an organizational unit producing goods or services. Industrial enterprises are classified as small versus large or medium-sized for their distinct nature of economic organization, production capacity, scale of investment, and other economic characteristics.Share of small business value added in total industry value addedNot available
			</language>
			<language lang="fr">Objectif 9. Bâtir une infrastructure résiliente, promouvoir une industrialisation durable qui profite à tous et encourager l’innovation9.3 Accroître, en particulier dans les pays en développement, l’accès des entreprises, notamment des petites entreprises industrielles, aux services financiers, y compris aux prêts consentis à des conditions abordables, et leur intégration aux chaînes de valeur et aux marchés9.3.1 Proportion des petites entreprises dans la valeur ajoutée totale de l’industrieLa proportion des «petites entreprises» dans la valeur ajoutée totale de l&apos;industrie représente la part de la valeur ajoutée manufacturière des petites entreprises manufacturières dans la valeur ajoutée manufacturière totale.       Une entreprise est la plus petite unité légale qui constitue une unité organisationnelle produisant des biens ou des services. Les entreprises industrielles sont classées de petites par rapport aux grandes ou moyennes pour leur nature distincte d&apos;organisation économique, de capacité de production, d&apos;échelle d&apos;investissement et d&apos;autres caractéristiques économiquesPart de la valeur ajoutée des petites entreprises dans la valeur ajoutée totale de l&apos;industrieNon disponible
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
